conductormax.com 2013-04-13

# Privacy Policy | Conductor MAX – My ACE Xpress

The purpose of this statement is to define ACE's policy with regards to the collection and use of information through use of the Conductor MAX website. 

**Anonymous Information**  
This type of information is transmitted by your browser and includes the URL of previous web page visited on the site, domain names or IP addresses assigned to your computer by your provider when you connect to the internet, and your browser version.

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
This type of information could include name, address, email address, telephone number, credit/debit card information. ACE will make every reasonable effort to protect your privacy. It restricts access to your personal identifiable information to those employees who will respond to your request. ACE does not intentionally disclose any personal information about our customers to any third parties except as required by law or by the consent of the person providing the information. ACE only collects personally identifiable information that is required to provide service.

**Email Addresses**  
Email addresses obtained through the Conductor MAX Web Site will not be sold or given to private companies for marketing purposes. Email or other information requests sent to the Conductor MAX Web Site may be maintained in order to respond to the request, forward that request to the appropriate department within the ACE or to provide the Conductor MAX web master with customer feedback to assist in improving the site.

**Cookies**  
Some Conductor MAX applications use cookies. A cookie is a small data file that writes to your hard drive if you allow them. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. Cookies can track user traffic patterns, recognize your computer’s browser when you return, and could provide personalized content without requiring sign-in. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. However, they may be required to use some of the web applications on the Conductor MAX site.

**Electronic Signatures and Payments**  
ACE is committed to data security and the data quality of personally identifiable information that is either available from or collected by our web site and has taken reasonable precautions to protect such information from loss, misuse, or alteration. When a Conductor MAX website application accepts credit cards or any other particularly sensitive information for any of its services, it encrypts all ordering information, such as your name and credit card number, in order to protect its confidentiality.
